A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12 FA284
Rockefeller Archive Center
- State Files, 2
  - Alabama - Budget Correspondence, February 21, 1938-January 8, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - Alabama - Budget Correspondence, February 21, 1938-January 8, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 152)
  - Alabama - Field Trip Reports, July 1937-May 1941 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - Alabama - Field Trip Reports, July 1937-May 1941 (Box 10, Folder 154)
  - Alabama - Financial Correspondence, August 22, 1938-August 18, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 155)
  - Alabama - General Correspondence, March 1, 1928-May 20, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 156)
  - Alabama - General Correspondence, March 1, 1928-May 20, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 157)
  - Arkansas - Budget and Financial Correspondence, December 15, 1944-June 30, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 158)
  - Arkansas - General Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, April 2, 1936-December 19, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 159)
  - California - General Correspondence and Field Report, December 2, 1943-July 11, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 160)
  - District of Columbia - General Correspondence and Field Reports, January 29, 1936-June 9, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 161)
  - Florida - Budget and Budget Correspondence, December 15, 1944-July 2, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Florida - Budget and Budget Correspondence, December 15, 1944-July 2, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - Florida - Field Technical Staff Reports, 1947-1950 (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - Florida - Field Technical Staff Reports, 1947-1950 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - Florida - Field Training Center - Correspondence, January 8, 1947-July 7, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - Florida - Field Training Center - Correspondence, January 8, 1947-July 7, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - Florida - Field Training Center - Correspondence, January 8, 1947-July 7, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - Florida - Field Training Center - Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - Florida - Field Training Center - Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 11, Folder 170)
  - Florida - Field Training Center - Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 11, Folder 171)
  - Florida - Field Training Center - Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - Florida - Field Trip Reports, January 16, 1942-November 22, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Florida - Field Trip Reports, January 16, 1942-November 22, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - Florida - Financial Correspondence, January 8, 1946-December 22, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - Florida - Financial Correspondence, January 8, 1946-December 22, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 176)
  - Florida - Financial Correspondence, January 9, 1948-February 20, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 177)
  - Florida - General Correspondence, January 13, 1944-October 14, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 178)
  - Florida - General Correspondence, January 13, 1944-October 14, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 179)
  - Florida - General Correspondence, January 13, 1944-October 14, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 180)
  - Florida - General Correspondence, January 13, 1944-October 14, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 181)
  - Florida - General Correspondence, January 13, 1944-October 14, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 182)
  - Kentucky - Barren County Reports, 1931-1937 (Box 12, Folder 183)
  - Kentucky - Barren County Reports, 1931-1937 (Box 12, Folder 184)
  - Kentucky - Barren County Reports, 1931-1937 (Box 12, Folder 185)
  - Kentucky - Barren County Reports, 1931-1937 (Box 12, Folder 186)
  - Kentucky - Budget and Financial Correspondence, December 15, 1944-March 19, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 187)
  - Kentucky - Field Trip Reports, May 2, 1935-June 4, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 188)
  - Kentucky - General Correspondence, January 13, 1944-July 30, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 189)
  - Kentucky - Vital Statistics Reports, January 8, 1945-March 5, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 190)
  - Louisiana - Budget and Budget Correspondence, September 29, 1945-January 18, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 191)
  - Louisiana - Field Training Center Reports, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 192)
  - Louisiana - Field Training Center Reports, 1948-1950 (Box 13, Folder 193)
  - Louisiana - Field Trip Reports, September 7, 1943-December 13, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 194)
  - Louisiana - Financial Correspondence, February 27, 1946-September 12, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 195)
  - Louisiana - General Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, August 6, 1935-November 29, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 196)
  - Louisiana - General Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, August 6, 1935-November 29, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 197)
  - Louisiana - General Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, August 6, 1935-November 29, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 198)
  - Louisiana - Report to the Commonwealth Fund Concerning Progress in the Louisiana Public Health Field Training Program 1945 to 1950 (Author: Dr. Ben Freedman), 1945-1950 (Box 13, Folder 199)
  - Louisiana - Report to the Commonwealth Fund Concerning Progress in the Louisiana Public Health Field Training Program 1945 to 1950 (Author: Dr. Ben Freedman), 1945-1950 (Box 13, Folder 200)
  - Maine - Memoranda, Field and Status Reports, November 9, 1931-June 15, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 201)
  - Maine - Memoranda, Field and Status Reports, November 9, 1931-June 15, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 202)
  - Maine - Statistical Summaries, 1928-1932 (Box 13, Folder 203)
  - Massachusetts - Applications to Enter District Health Unit, October-December 1930 (Box 13, Folder 204)
  - Massachusetts - Barnstable County Reports, September 1932 (Box 13, Folder 205)
  - Massachusetts - Budget and Budget Correspondence, August 12, 1930-December 14, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 206)
  - Massachusetts - Budget and Budget Correspondence, January 5, 1932-July 3, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 207)
  - Massachusetts - Budget and Budget Correspondence, January 5, 1932-July 3, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 208)
  - Massachusetts - Budget and Budget Correspondence, January 5, 1932-July 3, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 209)
  - Massachusetts - Cytologic Project - Correspondence and Reports, October 16, 1947-November 30, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 210)
  - Massachusetts - Cytologic Project - Correspondence and Reports, October 16, 1947-November 30, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 211)
  - Massachusetts - Division of Laboratories- Reports, June 1943-December 1945 (Box 14, Folder 212)
  - Massachusetts - Field Unit Reports, 1931-1936 (Box 14, Folder 213)
  - Massachusetts - General Correspondence and Reports, December 4, 1929-April 25, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 214)
  - Massachusetts - General Correspondence and Reports, December 4, 1929-April 25, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 215)
  - Massachusetts - General Correspondence and Reports, December 4, 1929-April 25, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 216)
  - Massachusetts - General Correspondence and Reports, December 4, 1929-April 25, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 217)
  - Massachusetts - General Correspondence and Reports, December 4, 1929-April 25, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 218)
  - Massachusetts - Harvard Correspondence and Reports, December 5, 1929-December 30, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 219)
  - Massachusetts - Harvard Correspondence and Reports, December 5, 1929-December 30, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 220)
  - Massachusetts - Harvard Correspondence and Reports, January 20, 1933-July 2, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 221)
  - Massachusetts - Harvard Correspondence and Reports, January 20, 1933-July 2, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 222)
  - Massachusetts - Harvard Correspondence and Reports, January 20, 1933-July 2, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 223)
  - Massachusetts - Harvard Correspondence and Reports, January 20, 1933-July 2, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 224)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Correspondence and Reports, February 13, 1931-June 16, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 225)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Correspondence and Reports, February 13, 1931-June 16, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 226)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Correspondence and Reports, February 13, 1931-June 16, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 227)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Correspondence and Reports, February 13, 1931-June 16, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 228)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Correspondence and Reports, February 13, 1931-June 16, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 229)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Correspondence and Reports, February 13, 1931-June 16, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 230)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Correspondence and Reports, February 13, 1931-June 16, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 231)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Correspondence and Reports, February 13, 1931-June 16, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 232)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Health Center Building - Correspondence, December 18, 1935-May 7, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 233)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Survey of Health Activities, 1930-1932 (Box 15, Folder 234)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Survey of Health Activities, 1930-1932 (Box 15, Folder 235)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Survey of Health Activities, 1930-1932 (Box 15, Folder 236)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Survey of Health Activities, 1933-1935 (Box 16, Folder 237)
  - Massachusetts - Nashoba Survey of Health Activities, 1933-1935 (Box 16, Folder 238)
  - Massachusetts - Requisitions and Financial Correspondence, October 24, 1930-January 28, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 239)
  - Massachusetts - Requisitions and Financial Correspondence, October 24, 1930-January 28, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 240)
  - Massachusetts - Requisitions and Financial Correspondence, October 24, 1930-January 28, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 241)
  - Massachusetts - Requisitions and Financial Correspondence, October 24, 1930-January 28, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 242)
  - Massachusetts - Requisitions and Financial Correspondence, October 24, 1930-January 28, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 243)
  - Massachusetts - Requisitions and Financial Correspondence, October 24, 1930-January 28, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 244)
  - Massachusetts - Requisitions and Financial Correspondence, October 24, 1930-January 28, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 245)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, November 12, 1930-May 18, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 246)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, November 12, 1930-May 18, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 247)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, November 12, 1930-May 18, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 248)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, November 12, 1930-May 18, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 249)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, July 9, 1934-March 27, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 250)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, July 9, 1934-March 27, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 251)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, July 9, 1934-March 27, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 252)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, July 9, 1934-March 27, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 253)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, July 9, 1934-March 27, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 254)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Survey of Health Activities, 1929-1935; 1938 (Box 17, Folder 255)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Survey of Health Activities, 1929-1935; 1938 (Box 17, Folder 256)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Survey of Health Activities, 1929-1935; 1938 (Box 17, Folder 257)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Survey of Health Activities, 1929-1935; 1938 (Box 17, Folder 258)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Survey of Health Activities, 1929-1935; 1938 (Box 17, Folder 259)
  - Massachusetts - Southern Berkshire Survey of Health Activities, 1929-1935; 1938 (Box 17, Folder 260)
  - Massachusetts - Tuberculosis Unit - Final Report, October 1, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 261)
  - Massachusetts - Tuberculosis Unit - Reports, April 1936-December 1939 (Box 17, Folder 262)
  - Massachusetts - Tufts University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, December 5, 1929-December 18, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 263)
  - Massachusetts - Tufts University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, December 5, 1929-December 18, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 264)
  - Massachusetts - Tufts University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, February 2, 1937-August 23, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 265)
  - Massachusetts - Tufts University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, February 2, 1937-August 23, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 266)
  - Massachusetts - Undergraduate Scholarships, September 28, 1933-September 11, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 267)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted - Confidential material. Requires prior archival review.
  - Mississippi - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, March 18, 1931-December 30, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 268)
  - Mississippi - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, March 18, 1931-December 30, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 269)
  - Mississippi - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, March 18, 1931-December 30, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 270)
  - Mississippi - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, March 18, 1931-December 30, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 271)
  - Mississippi - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, March 18, 1931-December 30, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 272)
  - Mississippi - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, March 18, 1931-December 30, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 273)
  - Mississippi - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, March 18, 1931-December 30, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 274)
  - Mississippi - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, March 18, 1931-December 30, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 275)
  - Mississippi - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, March 18, 1931-December 30, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 276)
  - Mississippi - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, March 18, 1931-December 30, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 277)
  - Mississippi - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, March 18, 1931-December 30, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 278)
  - Mississippi - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, January 10, 1947-June 16, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 279)
  - Mississippi - Clerical Training Program - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, June 23, 1942-August 18, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 280)
  - Mississippi - Epidemiological Unit - Correspondence and Reports
    - December 15, 1932-February 5, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 281)
    - December 15, 1932-February 5, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 282)
    - December 15, 1932-February 5, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 283)
    - December 15, 1932-February 5, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 284)
    - December 15, 1932-February 5, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 285)
  - Mississippi - Extension Education Program - Correspondence, July 8, 1936-June 28, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 286)
  - Mississippi - Extension Education Program - Correspondence, July 8, 1936-June 28, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 287)
  - Mississippi - Extension Education Program - Correspondence, July 8, 1936-June 28, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 288)
  - Mississippi - Field Trip Reports, May 15, 1930-October 4, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 289)
  - Mississippi - Field Trip Reports, May 15, 1930-October 4, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 290)
  - Mississippi - Field Trip Reports, May 15, 1930-October 4, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 291)
  - Mississippi - Field Unit Annual Report, July 1, 1940-June 30, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 292)
  - Mississippi - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 293)
  - Mississippi - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1932-1938 (Box 20, Folder 294)
  - Mississippi - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1932-1938 (Box 20, Folder 295)
  - Mississippi - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1932-1938 (Box 20, Folder 296)
  - Mississippi - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1932-1938 (Box 20, Folder 297)
  - Mississippi - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1932-1938 (Box 20, Folder 298)
  - Mississippi - Field Unit Report, January 1, 1931-June 30, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 299)
  - Mississippi - Field Unit Semiannual Reports, 1939-1946 (Box 20, Folder 300)
  - Mississippi - Field Unit Semiannual Reports, 1939-1946 (Box 20, Folder 301)
  - Mississippi - Field Unit Semiannual Reports, 1939-1946 (Box 20, Folder 302)
  - Mississippi - Financial Correspondence, December 15, 1931-November 24, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 303)
  - Mississippi - Financial Correspondence, December 15, 1931-November 24, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 304)
  - Mississippi - Financial Correspondence, December 15, 1931-November 24, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 305)
  - Mississippi - Financial Correspondence, December 15, 1931-November 24, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 306)
  - Mississippi - Financial Correspondence, December 15, 1931-November 24, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 307)
  - Mississippi - Financial Correspondence, February 26, 1944-September 22, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 308)
  - Mississippi - Financial Correspondence, February 26, 1944-September 22, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 309)
  - Mississippi - Financial Correspondence, February 26, 1944-September 22, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 310)
  - Mississippi - General Correspondence and Reports, December 4, 1929-February 18, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 311)
  - Mississippi - General Correspondence and Reports, December 4, 1929-February 18, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 312)
  - Mississippi - General Correspondence and Reports, December 4, 1929-February 18, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 313)
  - Mississippi - General Correspondence and Reports, December 4, 1929-February 18, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 314)
  - Mississippi - General Correspondence and Reports, December 4, 1929-February 18, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 315)
  - Mississippi - General Correspondence and Reports, December 4, 1929-February 18, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 316)
  - Mississippi - General Correspondence and Reports, December 4, 1929-February 18, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 317)
  - Mississippi - Jones County - Correspondence and Reports, November 9, 1935-June 21, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 318)
  - Mississippi - Jones County - Correspondence and Reports, November 9, 1935-June 21, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 319)
  - Mississippi - Jones County - Correspondence and Reports, November 9, 1935-June 21, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 320)
  - Mississippi - Jones County - Health Center Correspondence, January 6, 1942-August 31, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 321)
  - Mississippi - Jones County - Reports, 1938-1942; 1945 and 1947 (Box 22, Folder 322)
  - Mississippi - Jones County - Reports, 1938-1942; 1945 and 1947 (Box 22, Folder 323)
  - Mississippi - Jones County - Reports, 1938-1942; 1945 and 1947 (Box 22, Folder 324)
  - Mississippi - Jones County - Seven Year Review, 1937-1943 (Box 22, Folder 325)
  - Mississippi - Jones County - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1950 (Box 22, Folder 326)
  - Mississippi - Laboratory Reports, January 1, 1942-June 30, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 327)
  - Mississippi - Laboratory Reports, January 1, 1942-June 30, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 328)
  - Mississippi - Lauderdale County - Correspondence and Memoranda, June 5, 1931-June 30, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 329)
  - Mississippi - Lauderdale County - Correspondence and Memoranda, June 5, 1931-June 30, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 330)
  - Mississippi - Lauderdale County - Correspondence and Memoranda, June 5, 1931-June 30, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 331)
  - Mississippi - Lauderdale County - Health Center Correspondence, May 21, 1937-October 17, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 332)
  - Mississippi - Lauderdale County - Reports, 1930-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1942 (Box 22, Folder 333)
  - Mississippi - Lauderdale County - Reports, 1930-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1942 (Box 22, Folder 334)
  - Mississippi - Lauderdale County - Reports, 1930-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1942 (Box 22, Folder 335)
  - Mississippi - Lauderdale County - Reports, 1930-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1942 (Box 22, Folder 336)
  - Mississippi - Lauderdale County - Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 337)
  - Mississippi - Lauderdale County - Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 338)
  - Mississippi - Lauderdale County - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1950 (Box 23, Folder 339)
  - Mississippi - Lauderdale County - Study of Maternal Hygiene Services, 1931-1939 (Box 23, Folder 340)
  - Mississippi - Lee County - Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, March 10, 1932-February 10, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 341)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Correspondence and Memoranda, March 19, 1931-June 21, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 342)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Correspondence and Memoranda, March 19, 1931-June 21, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 343)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Correspondence and Memoranda, March 19, 1931-June 21, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 344)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Health Center Correspondence, December 16, 1936-July 20, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 345)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Reports, 1930-1935; 1938-1940; 1942; 1944; 1946 (Box 23, Folder 346)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Reports, 1930-1935; 1938-1940; 1942; 1944; 1946 (Box 23, Folder 347)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Reports, 1930-1935; 1938-1940; 1942; 1944; 1946 (Box 23, Folder 348)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Reports, 1930-1935; 1938-1940; 1942; 1944; 1946 (Box 23, Folder 349)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Reports, 1930-1935; 1938-1940; 1942; 1944; 1946 (Box 23, Folder 350)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Reports, 1930-1935; 1938-1940; 1942; 1944; 1946 (Box 23, Folder 351)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Reports, 1930-1935; 1938-1940; 1942; 1944; 1946 (Box 23, Folder 352)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1950 (Box 23, Folder 353)
  - Mississippi - Pike County - Survey of Health Activities, 1930-1940 (Box 23, Folder 354)
  - Mississippi - Public Health Fellowships - Correspondence and Applications, October 1, 1943-March 6, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 355)
  - Mississippi - Statistical Service - Correspondence and Reports, October 4, 1943-January 20, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 356)
  - Mississippi - Statistical Service - Correspondence and Reports, October 4, 1943-January 20, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 357)
  - Mississippi - Statistical Service - Correspondence and Reports, October 4, 1943-January 20, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 358)
  - Mississippi - Statistical Service - Correspondence and Reports, October 4, 1943-January 20, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 359)
  - Mississippi - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1945 (Box 24, Folder 360)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, April 20, 1927-October 26, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 361)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, April 20, 1927-October 26, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 362)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, April 20, 1927-October 26, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 363)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, April 20, 1927-October 26, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 364)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, April 20, 1927-October 26, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 365)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, April 20, 1927-October 26, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 366)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, April 20, 1927-October 26, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 367)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, April 20, 1927-October 26, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 368)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, April 20, 1927-October 26, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 369)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, November 1, 1949-September 21, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 370)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, November 1, 1949-September 21, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 371)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, November 1, 1949-September 21, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 372)
  - Mississippi - Tulane University - Reprints, March 1951-February 1953 (Box 25, Folder 373)
  - New Jersey - Evaluation Study - Annual Report, September 1, 1950-August 1, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 374)
  - New Jersey - Evaluation Study - Final Report, September 1953 (Box 25, Folder 375)
  - New Jersey - Field Unit - General and Financial Correspondence, Reports, January 9, 1951-December 7, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 376)
  - New Jersey - Field Unit - General and Financial Correspondence, Reports, January 9, 1951-December 7, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 377)
  - New Jersey - Field Unit - General and Financial Correspondence, Reports, January 9, 1951-December 7, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 378)